Guide to the Collection of Aerial Photographs 1935-2001
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
Collection of Aerial Photographs
1935-2001
Center for Pacific Northwest Studies Goltz-Murray Building 808 25th St Bellingham, WA 98225-9123 Phone: 360 650 7534 Email: cpnws@wwu.edu
XOE_CPNWS0318aerialphotos
80 linear feet
A collection of over 30,000 individual images from aerial surveys conducted in different areas of the Pacific Northwest (including northwest counties and National Forest Lands in Washington State).
Stereoscopes are available at CPNWS for use by researchers.
The Collection of Aerial Photographs was transferred to the Center for Pacific Northwest Studies in August 2011, as part of the former holdings of the Huxley Map Library at Western Washington University. The collection had been developed over the course of the Map Library's forty-year history, during which aerial images and flight indices appear to have been acquired gradually through donation or purchase. Since the time of the initial transfer, a small number of additional images have been donated and added to the collection at the Center for Pacific Northwest Studies.
The Collection of Aerial Photographs comprises over 30,000 individual images from aerial surveys conducted in different areas of the Pacific Northwest including the northwest counties and National Forest Lands of Washington State. The majority of images in the collection are from aerial surveys conducted by US government agencies, including the USDA Forest Service and Washington Department of Natural Resources. These include coverage of Whatcom County, the Mt. Baker National Forest and other National Forest and Parks lands in Washington. The collection also includes some coverage of other Washington counties and U.S. states. For example, a small group of images document survey work conducted for the Alaska-Canada Highway during the 1930s. The collection is a valuable resource for researchers interested in environmental history and change (including forestation, glaciation and waterways), and supports fields of inquiry relating to habitat restoration, urban growth studies and property history. Researchers should be aware that coverage for locations or flight surveys may not be comprehensive and that CPNWS cannot guarantee coverage and images for all areas of interest. In some cases, the collection may contain an index for a flight without any accompanying images (or vice versa).
The collection is arranged in two series:
Series I: Flight Index Sheets and Maps, 1938-2001
Series II: Aerial Photographs and Orthophotos, 1935-2000
The collection is open to the public, with the exception of Boxes 123-134 and Oversize Folders P1-P8 (restricted until further notice). Researchers are asked to contact CPNWS staff in advance and set up an appointment to access aerial images. Since this is a large and complex collection, it may take some time to determine which aerial surveys and images are relevant to your line of inquiry.
When contacting CPNWS, please provide us with as much information as possible about the area(s) of interest to you. For example:
Name(s) of towns, locations or geographical features.
Coordinates and/or Township/Range and Section information.
Time period or dates of interest.
Collection contents were developed by Huxley Map Library prior to the transfer of the collection to the Center for Pacific Northwest Studies in August 2011.
Duplicate materials were removed from the collection during processing.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Washington (State)--Aerial photographs; United States--Aerial photographs; Northwest, Pacific--Aerial photographs; Skagit County (Wash.)--Aerial photographs; Whatcom County (Wash.)--Aerial photographs; Island County (Wash.)--Aerial photographs; Baker, Mount (Wash.)--Aerial photographs
National parks and reserves--Washington (State)--Aerial photographs
Photographs
- Flight Index Sheets and Maps, 1938-2001; Series I
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1966; BBK; Department of Agriculture- Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service.; Pacific Aerial Surveys, Inc (Seattle, WA). (Folder A)
    Scale: 1:20,000
    Set of 4 photo index sheets. Township/Range marked. BBK-1GG through BBK-3GG.
  - Whatcom County, Washington., 1976; NW-C-76; Washington (State), Department of Natural Resources. (Folder A)
    Scale: 1:24,000
    Focal length 8.25”. Color and b/w. Includes 1 Skagit County image. Township and Range. Northwestern Washington, Enlargement of Whatcom County, Washington, includes Whatcom County, Washington, extension.
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1955; BBK; Washington (State), Department of Agriculture. Commodity Stabilization Service.; Aero Service Corp. (Folder B)
    Duplicate indices in Folders 00 and WWW. BBK-1P through BBK-3P.
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1943; L1 through L18; US Department of the Interior. (Folder C)
    Scale: Unknown.
    The letter L appears to represent flight line numbers. Index map is dated 1975.
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1947; BBK; United States. Department of Agriculture Agricultural Adjustment Administration.; C.S. Robinson Aerial Surveys. (Folder C)
    1 thru 6 (of 6 sheets), appears to be some British Columbia, Canada and Skagit County. BBK-1B through BBK-6B.
  - Nooksack River, Whatcom County, Washington, 1938 (Folder D)
    Scale: unknown
    Numbered flight lines.
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1995; NW95; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder D)
    Scale: 1:12,000
    Whatcom County, Washington.
    Index only - No photos for this flight available.
  - Whatcom County, Washington Aerial Photo Flight Index., 1978; NW-78; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder D)
    Two sheets (1 of 2, 2 of 2) + 3 duplicates of each sheet (one set is laminated).
  - Bellingham Flight Index - Whatcom County, Washington, 1979; 53073; United States. Department of Agriculture; WAC Corp. Euguene, OR (Folder D)
    Scale: 1:40,000
    Listed as Sheet 3 of 6.
  - Whatcom County, Washington Aerial Photography Flight Index., 1980; NWP-80; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder D)
    Two sheets: second sheet details flights between Van Zandt, Washington and Mt. Baker.
  - Whatcom County, Washington Aerial Photography Flight Index., 1987; NW-87; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder D)
    4 sheets + 3 duplicates of all 4 sheets (some revised in 1988).
  - Whatcom County, Washington Aerial Photography Flight Index., 1991; NW-91; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder D)
    3 of 5 sheets.
  - Bellingham Flight Index - Whatcom County, Washington, 1979; 53073; United States. Department of Agriculture.; WAC Corp. Euguene, OR (Folder E)
    Two Sheets: 2 of 6 and 3 of 6.
  - Whatcom County, Washington Aerial Photography Flight Index., 1983; NW-C-83; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder E)
    2 flight index sheets (1 of 2, 2 of 2), these include township and range, 3 dupicates of each sheet (one set is laminated).
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1963-1964; EMM; United States. Department of Agriculture Forest Service. (Folder F)
    Handwritten annotation: "S.O. Engineering." Map encapsulated February 2012.
  - Lummi Bay, Whatcom County, Washington, 1950; (possibly 'F' + number, eg F6-8, F9-31); Pacific Aerial Surveys (Folder F)
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1940; M (possibly); IF (possibly) (or combo); Geological Survey (U.S.) Project - Washington Boundary. (Folder G)
    Hand-drawn on tracing paper. Flight lines and image numbers included + 2 photocopies of Mt. Baker area enlarged.
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1947; GS-CJ; Geological Survey (U.S.).; Aero Service Corp. (Folder G)
    Scale: 1:126,720
    Flight line index and image numbers included, two pages of photocopied enlargements of Mt. Baker index area. The Chelan National Forest map in Folder NN continues lines of GS-CJ.
  - Mt. Baker, East Whatcom County, Washington, 1950; GS-LK; US Department of the Interior - Geological Survey. (Folder G)
    Scale: 1:47,200
    Folder includes eleven photocopied photo index sheets; handwritten on outside of folder "Quads for Mt. Baker, Mt. Shuksan, Hamilton, Lake Shannon, Marblemount, Copper Mountain a.k.a. Mt. Challenger."
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1964; . (Folder G)
    Flight line and image numbers included on 3 photocopied sheets.
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1972-1973; EXQ; United States. Department of Agriculture Forest Service. (Folder G)
    Scale: 1: 15,840
    Film type: color. 3 copies of flight index map + 2 photocopied enlargements of Mt. Baker area.
  - Mt. Baker, Washington Road Photography., 1961 July; MB; United States. Department of Agriculture Forest Service. (Folder G)
    Scale: 1:38,000
    Handwritten note that 17-8 and 17-9 are missing.
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1985; GS-VFGD-C-8 1/4; Geological Survey (U.S.). (Folder G)
    Index map of flight lines.
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1985-1987; GS-VFGD; Geological Survey (U.S.). (Folder G)
    Hand-drawn on tracing paper. Includes two 2 photocopies showing enlargement of Mt. Baker area.
  - Kititas County, Washington Aerial Photograph Flight Index., 1979; KYK-79; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder H)
    Set of 4 sheets.
  - Kititas County, Washington Aerial Photograph Flight Index., 1984-1985; SC-C-84; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder H)
    4 sheets.
  - Klickitat County, Washington, 1979; KYK-79; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder I)
    5 sheets (sets of 2 and 3 sheets).
  - Klickitat County, Washington, 1984; SC-C-84; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder I)
    Set of 3 sheets.
  - Kitsap County, Washington, 1985; SP-85; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder J)
    4 sheets (2 sets of 2 sheets).
  - Lewis County, Washington, 1978; SW-C-78; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder K)
  - Marysville, Washington, NE and NW Quads., 1954; GS-VBR; Geological Survey (U.S.). (Folder L)
    Scale: 1:23,600
    2 sheets (1 of 2, 2 of 2), these include township and range, 3 dupicates of each sheet (one set is laminated).
  - Mason County, Washington, 1985; SP-85; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder L)
    2 sets of 3 sheets.
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1973; OL-H-73; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder M)
    Scale: 1:58,000
  - Olympic National Forest, Washington, Road Photography, 1964; OLY 64 (Folder M)
    Flight line numbers included.
  - Olympic National Forest, Washington, Road Photography, 1965; OLY 65 (Folder M)
  - Olympic National Forest, Washington, Road Photography, 1981; OL 81 (Folder M)
  - Olympic National Forest, Washington, Road Photography, 1990; OL 90 (Folder M)
    Flight line numbers included on 3 map sheets.
  - Olympic National Forest, Washington, Road Photography, 1997; OL 97 (Folder M)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1964; ONF (Folder M)
  - Olympic National Forest, Washington, Index to Aerial Photography, 1972; 53031 (Folder M)
    Scale: 1:70,000
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, Flight Index, 1977; OL-77; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder M)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington Flight Index, 1977; OL-77A (Folder M)
    Large, hand-drawn map.
  - Olympic National Forest, Washington, Index of Aerial Photographs, 1939; GS-J; Geological Survey (U.S.). (Folder M)
    Scale: 1:30,000
    See also EEEE.
  - Olympic National Forest, Washington Index (handwritten), 1985; GS-VFHA (Folder M)
    Handwritten note on back: "From 1-168 to 5-167," Latitude and Longitude.
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1980; OL-H-80 (Folder M)
    Hand-drawn map.
  - Olympic National Forest, Washington, Photo Strips of New Road Construction, 1959; OR-59; United States. Department of Agriculture Forest Service. (Folder M)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1967, 1979-1980; WFPA-66; 626090 (Folder M)
    Photostatic map with 2 different sets of flight lines (WFPA-66 and 626090).
  - Pacific County, Washington, 1978; SW-C-78; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder N)
    Set of 2 sheets.
  - Pierce County, Washington, 1985; SP-85; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder O)
    2 sets of 5 sheets.
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1978; NW-78 (Folder P)
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1983; NW-C-83 (Folder P)
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1991; NW-91 (Folder P)
  - San Juan County, Washington, 1983; NW-C-83; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder Q)
  - Skamania County, Washington, 1978; SW-C-78 (Folder R)
  - Spokane County, Washington, 1957; AAN; USA Commodity Stabilization Service.; Western Aerial Contractors, Inc. (Folder S)
    Nine photo-index sheets.
  - Stevens County, Washington, 1957; BBD (Folder T)
  - Bonney Lake, Washington, 1995; Bonney Lake Block (Folder U)
    Photo stat index sheet plus aerial photographs of Bonney Lake, Washington (color).
  - Stevens County, Washington, 1968; BBD; Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service.; Western Aerial Contractors, Inc. (Folder U)
    Set of 10 photo indices.
  - Wahkiakum County, Washington Flight Paths for EOR 2FF-4FF, 1965; EOR (Folder V)
    Hand-drawn flight lines on traced map.
  - Thurston County, Washington, 1954; BBH (Folder W)
  - Thurston County, Washington, 1985; SP-85; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder W)
  - Wahkiakum County, Washington, 1978; SW-C-78; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder W)
    Sheet 1 of 1.
  - Snohomish County, Washington, 1978; NW-78; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder X)
  - Spokane County, Washington, 1986; NE-86; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder X)
  - Snohomish County, Washington Aerial Photo Index, 1983; NW-C-83; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder Y)
    4 index map sheets with flight lines (Revisions: 2-1983, 1-1984, 1-1985. some photos for this flight have non-corresponding flight numbers.
  - Chehalis County, Washington, 1980; GS-VEYV; Geological Survey (U.S.). (Folder Z)
    1 index sheet.
  - Clallam County, Washington, 1979; OBD-79; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder AA)
    1 set of 2 sheets.
  - Clallam County, Washington, 1985; OL-85; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder AA)
    2 sets of 4 sheets.
  - Clark County, Washington, 1978; SW-C-78; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder BB)
    1 set of 1 sheet. Folder includes aerial photos of Columbia River and Toutle River, Washington, dated Aug. 9, 1981).
  - Cowlitz County, Washington, 1978; SW-C-78; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder BB)
  - Cowlitz County, Washington, 1964; ENJ (Folder CC)
    1 traced map with flight lines hand-drawn.
  - Douglas County, Washington, 1979; OC-C-79; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder DD)
  - Douglas County, Washington, 1965; AAQ; Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service. (Folder DD)
    6 of 11 sheets (some dupl., some partials).
  - Grant County, Washington, 1955; AAR; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Aero Service Corp. (Folder EE)
    Sheets 1, 2, 3, 5, 6, 10 of 10 photo sheets.
  - Grays Harbor County, Washington, 1985; OL 85; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder FF)
  - Island County, Washington, 1963; ELU (Folder GG)
  - Island County, Washington, 1978; NW-78; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder HH)
  - Island County, Washington, 1983; NW-C-83; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder HH)
    2 sets of 1 index sheet.
  - Jefferson County, Washington, 1979; OBD-79; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder II)
  - Jefferson County, Washington, 1985; OL 85; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder II)
    2 sets of 5 sheets (no sheet 3 marked).
  - Jefferson County, Washington, 1981; OL-81; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder JJ)
  - Pierce County, Washington, Aerial Flight Index, 1955; M 55-4; Carl M. Berry Aerial Surveys (Folder KK)
    Pierce County, Washington: Anderson Is., Dupont, Steilacoom; University Place, Fircrest, Tacoma; American Lake, Steilacoom Lake, Lakewood. Photo marked King County, but are Pierce County, Washington.
  - King County, Washington, Aerial Flight Index, 1985; SP-85; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder KK)
    2 sets of 6 maps.
  - Klickitat County, Washington, 1971; AAS-1MM (Folder LL)
    Hand-traced map with flight lines.
  - King County, Washington, Aerial Flight Index, 1978; NW-78; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder LL)
    Set of 4 sheets flight index.
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1956-57; CWD; Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service.; Pacific Aerial Surveys. (Folder MM)
    Set of 6 sheets. CWD-1R through CWD-5R.
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1941; GS (Folder MM)
    Handwritten annotation on photostat map.
  - Chelan County, Washington, 1979; OC-C-79; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder NN)
    Set of 5 sheets.
  - Chelan National Forest, Washington, 1947; GS-CJ; Geological Survey (U.S.). (Folder NN)
    Scale: 1:27,700
    Mt. Baker Nat'l Forest photo index map in Folder G continues lines of GS-CJ.
  - Holden, Washington, 1963 (Folder NN)
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1955; BBK; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Aero Service Corp. (Folder OO)
    Seems to duplicate Folder B, WWW.
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1967; CWD (1GG-4GG); Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service. (Folder PP)
    Index 3 of 5 (26 copies), 4 sheets (index maps).
  - Klickitat County, Washington, 1954; AAS; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Hycom Aerial Surveys. (Folder QQ)
    Set of 9 sheets. AAS-1N through AAS-7N.
  - San Juan County, Washington Aerial Index, 1995; NW95; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder RR)
  - Skagit County, Washington Aerial Index, 1995; NW95; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder RR)
  - Island County, Washington Aerial Index, 1995; NW95; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder RR)
  - Douglas County, Washington, 1965; AAQ; United States. Department of Agriculture Agricultural and Stabilization Service.; Southern Mapping and Engineering Company. (Folder SS)
    Sheets 5 and 6 of 11 only (multiple copies).
  - Okanogan County, Washington, 1964; COD; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder TT)
    3 Photo index sheets.
  - Okanogan County, Washington, 1979; OC-C-79 (Folder TT)
    Set of 6 index map sheets.
  - Yakima County, Washington, 1979; KYK-79; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder UU)
  - Yakima County, Washington, 1984; SC-C-84; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder UU)
  - Mt. St. Helens, Washington, 1980, 1982; MSH-C-80; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder VV)
    Index map is for 1980, but annotations in blue are for 1982 flight.
  - Mt. St. Helens and vicinity, Washington, 1981; LVINV (Folder VV)
    Hand-drawn map (color pencil) includes Columbia River
  - Chugach National Forest, Alaska, Area A, 1959; EEV; United States. Department of Agriculture Forest Service...; James W. Sewall Company. (Folder W W)
    Scale: 1:15,840
    Sheet 10.
  - Chugach National Forest, Alaska, Area C, 1960; EEV; United States. Department of Agriculture Forest Service.; James W. Sewall Company. (Folder W W)
    Sheet 3.
  - Chugach National Forest, Alaska, Area C, 1961; EEV; United States. Department of Agriculture Forest Service.; James W. Sewall Company. (Folder W W)
    Sheets 5 and 9.
  - Chugach National Forest, Alaska, Area C, 1962; EEV; United States. Department of Agriculture Forest Service.; James W. Sewall Company. (Folder W W)
    Sheet 13.
  - Wayne County, Michigan, 1957; XU; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Robert and Son Aerial Surveys, Inc. (Folder XX)
  - Waseca County, Minnesota, 1956; WE; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Mid-West Aerial Surveys. (Folder YY)
    Sheet 1.
  - Le Sueur County, Minnesota, 1958; WF; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Park Aerial Surveys. (Folder YY)
  - Rice County, Minnesota, 1958; WG; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Park Aerial Surveys. (Folder YY)
  - Dallas County, Texas, 1958; DJU; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Fort Wayne Aerial Surveys. (Folder ZZ)
  - Western Washington (State), 1969-1970; NW-69; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder AAA)
    Sheets 1 and 2 of 2 (Front to Back, 2 copies + one photocopy); 1 Large map.
  - Washington State, 1939-1966; A; B; C; D; GS; TG; AAQ; AAS; AAU; BBD; CCH; CCI; DDA; ASOT; WHIT; Washington (State) Department of Highways (DOT). (Folder AAA)
    Scale: 1:500,000
  - Mt. Baker, Snoqualmie, Wenatchee National Forests, 1979; 616050; United States. Department of Agriculture Forest Service.; WAC Corporation (Folder AAA)
  - Okanogan National Forest, Washington, 1979; OC-C-79 (Folder AAA)
    Scale: 1:18,500
  - Wenatchee National Forest, Washington, 1979; OC-C-79 (Folder AAA)
  - Kern County, California, 1958; ABL; United States. Department of Agriculture. (Folder BBB)
    6 sheets of 16 (1, 2, 9, 10, 11, 16).
  - San Luis Obispo County, California, 1957; AXH; United States. Department of Agriculture. (Folder CCC)
    6 sheets of 16 (4-7, 14, 15).
  - Fairfield County, Connecticut, 1951; DPD; United States. Department of Agriculture. (Folder DDD)
    Set of 5 Sheets.
  - Lassen County, California, 1954; BUV; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Clyde Sunderland. (Folder EEE)
    Sheets 4 and 5 of 21.
  - Mono County, California, 1951; GS-QN; Geological Survey (U.S.).; Mark Hurd Mapping Company. (Folder EEE)
    2 sheets (dupl.) Mono Craters, 1 sheet Merced Peak.
  - Tuolumne County, California, 1955; GS-VJS; United States. Department of Agriculture.; Transworld Engineering Corp. (Folder EEE)
    Scale: 1:47,000
    1 Sheet.
  - Newell, California, 1948; GS-ECA; Geological Survey (U.S.).; Park Aerial Surveys (Folder EEE)
    Scale: 1:27,230
    1 sheet.
  - San Diego County, California, 1939; AXN; United States. Department of Agriculture.; Fairchild Aerial Surveys (Folder EEE)
    Sheets 1 of 5.
  - Santa Rosa Island, Santa Barbara County, California, 1940; BTM; United States. Department of Agriculture.; Fairchild Aerial Surveys (Folder EEE)
    Sheet 5 of 6.
  - Leadville Quad, Colorado, (Leadville now Holy Cross on photo), 1944; GS-GH; Geological Survey (U.S.).; Aero Service Corp. (Folder FFF)
  - Loveland (NE), Colorado, 1958; GS-CHR; Geological Survey (U.S.).; Mark Hurd Aerial Surveys, Inc (Folder FFF)
    Scale: 1:62,500
  - Las Animas County, Colorado (Spanish Peaks, Colorado), 1958; AXP; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Park Aerial Surveys (Folder FFF)
    Sheets 7 and 8 of 22.
  - Volusia County, Florida, 1958; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; General Aerial Surveys (Folder GGG)
    Sheet 8.